<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>official on Deplebify</title>
    <link>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/tags/official/</link>
    <description>Recent content in official on Deplebify</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/tags/official/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reddit bakeoff</title>
      <link>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/post/redditbakeoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/post/redditbakeoff/</guid>
      <description>In July 2020 Reddit announced a competition titled The Great Reddit Scaling Bake-Off and invited teams to demonstrate how their technology could provide the back-end for a Reddit points architecture on Ethereum mainnet.
 &amp;ldquo;tl;dr: Do you believe your Ethereum scaling technology can handle Reddit&amp;rsquo;s scale? It&amp;rsquo;s time to let the Ethereum community hear about it. Send your demo by July 31, 2020.&amp;rdquo;
 The OMG team duly stepped up with one of the strongest proposals, a virtual demo:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitfinex</title>
      <link>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/post/bitfinex/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/post/bitfinex/</guid>
      <description>Official announcement In June 2020 OMG Network announced that Bitfinex will integrate Tether (USDt) on the OMG network:
 “Today, we’re excited to announce the launch of the OMG Network that supports thousands of transactions per second and reduces transaction costs to a third of Ethereum,” said Vansa Chatikavanij, CEO at OMG Network. “We’re delighted to partner with Bitfinex to address blockchain’s scalability issues and drive further growth and adoption of open financial services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toyota</title>
      <link>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/post/toyota/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icy-bay-0b0640403.azurestaticapps.net/post/toyota/</guid>
      <description>Official announcement On the 22nd June 2020 Jun tweeted:
Read the official TFS press release here! Toyota Financial Services is the financial arm of #Toyota Group. They help millions of Toyota customers drive the vehicle of their dreams with their flexible financial and lease programs. #SYNQA #Omise #OMGnetworkhttps://t.co/a9ZgdoGi0n
&amp;mdash; JUNΞ 潤 (@JUN_SYNQA) June 22, 2020 The press release (Google) translates to (added links are mine):
&amp;ldquo;Investment in SYNQA (formerly Omise Holdings) Toyota Financial Services Co.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>